vivapersia.com 2008-09-15

# Viva Persia| Terms of Service and Privacy Policy

Terms of Service 

**Your Use of the Site**  
VivaPersia.com hereby grants you a limited license to copy and use the materials, features, and services provided by VivaPersia.com on this Site (collectively the "Materials") solely for your personal, non-commercial use, subject to these Terms. The design and layout of the Site are specifically excluded from the Materials. No other use of the Site or Materials is authorized. You agree that any copy of the Materials (or any portion of the Materials) that you make shall retain all copyright and other proprietary notices contained herein or therein. Framing of the Site or Site Materials or posting of Materials on other Web Sites is strictly prohibited. 

The products, technology, and/or processes described and/or used on this Site may be the subject of intellectual property rights reserved by VivaPersia.com or other third parties. Except for the limited license granted above, nothing contained herein shall be construed as conferring to you in any manner, whether by implication, estoppel or otherwise, any license, title, or ownership of or to any intellectual property right of VivaPersia.com or any third party.

**Acceptable Use Policy**  
VivaPersia.com has adopted the following Acceptable Use Policy in order to assure that its electronic greetings are used in a lawful and appropriate manner. While VivaPersia.com does not ordinarily monitor the content of users' greetings, it reserves the right to investigate reports of misuse of its service and to protect its property and assets. The following conduct is prohibited on the service: 

  * sending harassing, abusive, or threatening messages; 
  * sending obscene or pornographic messages or images; 
  * sending defamatory or libelous messages; 
  * sending viruses or other harmful, disruptive, or destructive files; 
  * attempting to steal passwords or credit card information; 
  * sending messages in furtherance of unlawful, criminal, or fraudulent activity; or 
  * attempting to conceal or misrepresent the identity of the sender. 

**Spam**  
You may not use this Site to send online greeting cards to mailing lists to which you do not have full rights or to send unsolicited bulk or commercial messages. In addition, the use of automated scripting-type programs that automate the process of sending or viewing any of the Materials is strictly prohibited. VivaPersia.com reserves the right to limit, in its sole discretion and without prior notice to you, the number of cards or messages that you may send using the Site and/or the number of recipients to which you send such cards or messages. 

You are solely responsible for your actions and communications undertaken or transmitted using this Site. Neither we nor our affiliates exercise editorial control over your transmissions; however, we do reserve the right to review your uploads and transmissions in order to ensure compliance with these Terms.

**Creating Your Own Greetings and Photos and/or Images**  
VivaPersia.com may allow you to create your own greetings by uploading your own photos, artwork and other materials. If we do and you do so, you are subject to the conditions outlined in these Terms. When you upload photos and/or images to the Site you are indicating that you own the photo and/or image and/or have full rights to its use.

When you upload material to the Site and use it to create a greeting, your material will be used for the transmission of your digital greeting; however, we may also use such material in the course of performing testing, training and/or archiving of our and our affiliates' systems and hereby expressly reserve the right to do so.

Privacy Policy  

**Overview**  
At VivaPersia.com, protecting our users' privacy and security is a top priority. For this reason, we have adopted the following policy to advise you of your choices regarding the use of your personal information online. This policy describes what types of information we gather about you, how we use it, under what circumstances we disclose it to third-parties, and your rights to update or correct it.

**Aggregate Data**  
We gather certain generic information with respect to customers' use of our web site, such as the number of unique visitors, the frequency with which they visit, and the areas on the web site that they favor. These statistics are very much like television ratings that tell the networks how many people tuned in to a program. We only use this type of data in aggregate-that is, we look at the data on a collective basis, in summary form, rather than on an individual basis. This data helps us determine the extent to which our customers use certain parts of our web site, which, in turn, enables us to make it as appealing as possible. We may also provide statistical "ratings" about how our customers collectively use our web site to advertisers, sponsors, and other companies with which we do business ("Business Partners"). We do this so they, too, can understand how often people use their areas of the site in order for them to provide you with the best possible experience. These statistical ratings do not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any of our users.

**IP Addresses**  
We collect and analyze traffic on our web site by keeping track of the IP addresses of our visitors. IP addresses are unique numeric identifiers that are assigned to each computer browser accessing the Internet. An IP address, by itself, cannot identify you personally. However, when combined with other information provided by your Internet Service Provider (ISP), your IP address can be used to identify the computer originating a message.

**When You Send A Greeting**  
If you use our web site to send a greeting or any other content, we collect your e-mail address and your recipient's e-mail/mailing address. This information is necessary to send the content and provide confirmation that it has been received. We will not use your recipient's e-mail/mailing address for any purpose other than to send the greeting. We may also use your e-mail address to contact you if you have chosen to receive communications from VivaPersia.com or its Partners.

**Privacy of Greeting Card Information**  
We treat all of our greetings products as private correspondence between the sender and the recipient and will not disclose the contents of any greeting other than to the intended recipient, except under the specific situations outlined in Disclosure Exceptions, below. This policy applies to all aspects of our greetings, including your personalized messages. Under normal circumstances, we will not monitor or edit the contents of the online greetings you send. On occasion, however, we may need to view your message in connection with the technical processing of your greeting or the maintenance of our network. Also, if you ask one of our customer service representatives to help you send a greeting or to verify that a greeting was sent, that representative will be able to access all information about the card, including the recipient's e-mail address and the message.   
_  
_**Disclosure Exceptions**  
Notwithstanding the above policies, we reserve the right to disclose your personal information to appropriate third-parties if we are required to do so by law or we believe that such action is necessary: 

  * To comply with legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order; 
  * To protect the company's rights and property; 
  * To investigate reports of users sending material using a false e-mail address or users sending harassing, threatening, or abusive messages; 
  * To protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our web site and/or the VivaPersia.com service; or 
  * During emergencies, such as when we believe someone's physical safety is at risk.
